[{"answer": "I'll do what I can, but I can't work miracles.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "Now can he help me with my game?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean -- I mean think I know more than anyone else from this year's Masters, you know, what happened to me, it's, you know, 95 percent of it is mental.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "When it actually comes down to it, when you're entering that fourth day as you did, what is it that makes a champion compared to others who often fall by the wayside?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know I felt as if the reception I got from the American people was very good.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How did they react to this young whippersnapper from Ireland coming in and winning their trophy?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "He was fantastic all week.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "How did your dad react to this?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Never Guinness.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Now which is it?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "Never Guinness?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "No, I'm not -- I'm not a big fan.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "You don't like Guinness?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "You know, personally I've never seen the violence.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "For a young man growing up as you did there, what was it like for you?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "A little bit, but I don't mind that.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you feel that the weight of the expectation of the Irish on your shoulders?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It's hard.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Or can you be both?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "That's probably the diplomatic answer, isn't it?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Did you have a tough upbringing, would you say?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "My dad was a bar manager and worked in separate places, you know, in the daytime and then in the night.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What did they do?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "It's been worth it, though, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Yes, it's --", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you were growing up and the other Hollywood, that the real one, one day would be a place that would welcome you like a conquering hero?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Pretty surreal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Yes, it's -- I mean -- I didn't realize how much attention and focus was going to be on me after that.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "It must have turned things upside down, isn't it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "CILROY: No, it's exciting.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Is it exciting or slightly terrifying?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "They've been very positive.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "How have they reacted, the guys who've never won and tried for so long to do so?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, you know, at 22 we both had one major.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "Do you see any parallels with Tiger in terms of the way you play?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "That's a lot of pressure, isn't it?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "It's part of the thing in sports to not be in awe of people?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Do you think you have the strength of character to deal with it in a way that Tiger ultimately turned out not to have?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "It's not -- it's not a healthy way to live for relationships and stuff, is it?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "She -- I mean -- I think in a way it's tough on her.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What does she make of what's happening to you?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "No, not at the moment.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think wedding bells on the horizon here?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Does it depend on how good a degree she gets?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "I mean even with him, you want to kill him, right, on the golf course?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I think you need that.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Where have you got that from?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Probably with a slap from the back of her right hand.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "I mean if you tried to go home to Holly and the two dogs with the swagger and the arrogance and the cockiness, how would she react?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I think for any golfer from my generation, watching Tiger -- you know growing up and winning his major championships was a huge inspiration for me to believe that, you know, maybe one day I could go on to emulate what he's done.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Who's most inspired you?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "No, he left a message in the media center.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Did he call you after the U.S. Open?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Just well done, great performance from start to finish.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Saying what?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "And not that well known in America, but in terms of his leadership, is he someone that inspires you?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "No, if anything it made me more determined to go back and to prove to a lot of people, not just the media but you know just everyone and prove to myself as well that I wasn't this person that they were making me out to be in the press, you know, a choker or you know can't handle the pressure.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Did you sink into a kind of temporary oblivion of despair?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "A little bit, yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Can you relax?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I think to go and watch other sports -- sporting event.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What was the best escape route for you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Do you ever read books?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Yes, music.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Music -- do you listen to music?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I lot of -- lot of dancy, sort of techno, Swedish House Mafia, David Guetta.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What's on your iPod?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "All that sort of stuff, yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Personally, not to let all this attention that I'm going to probably get -- not let that affect me in any way.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What's the big ambition for you, personally and professionally?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "The best golfer in history?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I would probably be --", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Is that now attainable to you, do you think?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Probably.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Did you throw the ball to me?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I've gone every single year since '61.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "ING: Well, I got to a point -- because I started having my first knee operation when I was 23 and I was number one in the world.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Do you still play tennis?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I've had eight altogether on my knees.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "How many surgeries have you had now?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I just played tennis the last two days out in Central Park in New York City.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "It's really worked?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "No, I'm terrible.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Are you good these days?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "When I found out, I was in Japan.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "What were you thinking when that happened?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "So Margaret took one for the team by losing.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Because you had to shut him up, right?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Such relief, thank you, God.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "ORGAN: When you beat him, how did that moment feel?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I'd actually get half and half.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "When you went out afterwards, what was the reaction from women in particular to what you'd done?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Just to really think about always making sure his daughters or girls and women have opportunities just like boys.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Influenced him to do what?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I think it's because I got into tennis when I was 11.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Did something happen to spark that?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "It did.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "That in itself created shock waves, didn't it?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Yes, which I thought was a great compliment.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I think for me, probably being gay, being a lesbian.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "What was the hardest barrier for you to break down, do you think?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "Endorsements went bye-bye in 24 hours.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "From what, endorsements?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "In the long run, sure.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Looking back on it, did its actually make your life better in the longer terms?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Because it's not right.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Why would you advise other people not to come out?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Forever.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Have you stayed friends with Elton?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Have you seen his new baby yet?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "This generation is so much better.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "How would you have got on against women who are so physically powerful?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "you're really asking difficult questions, because it depends.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "What's been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Actually not.", "docId": "110630pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "Does anything beat the first one?", "qSentId": 729}]